aofas.org 2009-04-28

# AOFAS Privacy Statement and Usage Disclosure

**AOFAS Privacy Statement and Usage Disclosure  
**  
AOFAS values your privacy. This Privacy Statement will make you aware of our privacy practices so you can rest assured you have a complete understanding of how we respect your privacy and the steps we will take to safeguard your privacy.  
AOFAS does not sell or rent your personal information to third parties without your explicit consent (this includes consent via e-mail). Nor does AOFAS use any information about your use of the site to market to you directly.

AOFAS does not retain or use personal information about your use of our site. AOFAS may collect and track various non-personal information based on your use of this site for our internal purposes in furtherance of serving our users, such as your IP address, the URL address you came from, and the URL address you go to next. This information is aggregated and is not used or disclosed by AOFAS in a personally-identifiable manner.

For AOFAS members who sign in to the members-only areas of the site, AOFAS will place a “cookie” on your computer when you sign in which is removed when you sign out. We may use cookie information to determine the popularity of certain content or services. Your browser software may be set to reject all cookies. Most browsers offer instructions on how to reset the browser to reject cookies in the "Help" section of the toolbar. If you reject our cookie, certain of the functions and conveniences of our site may not work properly but you do not have to accept our cookie in order to productively use our site. You are responsible for the confidentiality of your password.

Our site may contain links to other Web sites. Once you leave www.aofas.org and its sub-domains, the use and protection of your personal information is governed by the privacy policy at that site. You should review the privacy policy of other sites you visit or link to from our site to understand how these other sites use cookies and how they use the information they collect through the use of cookies or web beacons on their own sites. 

Our Privacy Policy does not protect you when you send business information, ideas, concepts or inventions to AOFAS by e-mail to any AOFAS e-mail address listed throughout the site. If you want to keep business information, ideas, concepts or inventions private or proprietary, do not send them in an e-mail to AOFAS. 

We try to answer every e-mail in a timely manner, but are not always able to do so.

For members and others who register for courses and meetings or make purchases or dues payments through our site, we retain registration and purchase information. We do not retain credit card numbers from financial transactions.  
Your information is stored on professionally hosted and backed up servers in the United States. AOFAS uses Secure Socket Layers to protect your information. Any credit card information you provide will be encrypted though the latest techniques.

AOFAS reserves the right to amend this policy at any time. Your continued use of this site constitutes your acceptance of any future amendments to this policy. Though we are committed to ensuring your privacy, we may be required to disclose personal information when required by law and when necessary to comply with a court order or other legal process.  
Any questions about this Privacy Statement may be directed to the Society at aofasinfo@aofas _dot_ org or you may call the Society at 800-235-4855 or 847-698-4654.
